







Summary

Jump to Section

Project Manager with 7+ years of experience driving projects for Strategy, Digital Transformation, and Cloud enablement for Banking and financial services Domain

Expertise in driving digital transformation and process re-engineering projects to support organization change management

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Experience of Agile project management, project execution lifecycle and liaising with multiple agile teams Tech Consulting experience for transforming client ecosystems across People, Process, Technology and tools, having good hold over application portfolio for banks and financial instituions

Proficient in working with CXO level stakeholders and senior leadership to understand their expectations and organizational constraints

Work Experience

 L&T Infote ch as Consultant (Cloud Infrastructure and Services) -IT Jan 2020 to Till Date

Program Management

Develop business cases for automation, data in sighting and digital transformation, after thorough gap analysis and scope definition

Creating Project charters, Project schedules, Risk mitigation plans, Cost management proposal and Resource management metrices for successful project deliveries.

Carry out implementation of industry best practices such as Agile, Scaled Agile and DevOps by leveraging Microsoft technology stack. Exposure to 3rd party software such as VMware Cloud foundation, MuleSoft, concepts such as containerization and Microservices

Leverage project management tools such as MPP, SCORO, SharePoint, Tableau, JIRA Rally and WORKZONE and frameworks such as Scrum and Kanban to ensure seamless project/program delivery and accurate checkpoint reviews

LTI "Employee of the Quarter" award for Outstanding performance as Project Manager for large US based banking client

Crafting RFP responses and cloud enabled transformation roadmaps, working across verticals to derive customer value

o Created proposal for a large client to accelerate their cloud migration journey on Mcrosoft winning a proposal of \$1.9 MI USD

BMC Software India Pvt. Ltd as Project Analyst

Feb 2016 to Jan 2019

Project Management

Spearheading the implementation of 'Cloud First' strategy across the organization Led teams of 20, for successful delivery of 14 global transformation projects at BMC Software

1

Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld. Consulted and Managed the initiative of SharePoint migration, thereby moving 18TB of content to SharePoint Online

Leveraged migration tools such as Sharegate to streamline analysis and migration across various project phases

Implemented SAFe framework and Agile release train approach for timely completion of the project Managed multiple digitization projects for improving employee & customer engagement practices at BMC as part of the industry 4.0 initiatives working extensively with Salesforce BMC 'Spot Award' for successful delivery- annual savings of \$6 million for the organization

Qualtech Consultants India Pvt. Ltd as Senior Systems Analyst Sep 2015 to Feb 2016

Project Management & Systems Analyst

Managed implementations of enterprise mobility applications for Fintech clients
Analysed client's problem statements to ideate and design use cases for new features of the product
Performed functional testing and provided demos of product features to clients
Created deployment, warranty and support plans for launch of mobile applications for financial services
products

Pre-sales

Secured US \$3 million project by jointly working with sales team in customer acquisition proposals

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E (Electrical and Electronics) from BCET, Durgapur in 2011

PG: MBA/PGDM (Information Technology) from SPJIMR, Mumbai in 2019

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs: Certificate course in Business Management

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used	Experience
Microstrategy, PWA		
SharePoint, Mcrosoft project plan		
Axure, MS excel		
Scaled Agile Framework		
AWS	2020	2 Year(s) 6 Month(s)

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Expert	✓	✓	✓
Hindi	Expert	✓	✓	✓

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: General Job Type: Permanent
Physically Challenged: No Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQs - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.